

## Olga Neiasova

Female, married, 36 y.o., London, UK

Contact

olga\_neyasova@yahoo.com

#### **Profile**

I am originally from Russia, have been living in the UK for 3 years, and before that for 1.5 years in Canada. Before emigrating, I had experience mostly in sales in various areas. Thanks to my previous work, I developed the ability to communicate effectively with clients, stress resistance, responsibility, teamwork skills, and determination. But I have always had an interest in technology, so one day I started an online programming course and found out that I like writing code. During emigration, I decided to completely change my career to the IT domain. After moving abroad, I studied English and French, and also began to learn Python, took online courses on programming and tech support.

### **Experience**

Jan 2017 - Dec 2018 St Petersburg, Russia Managing Director, "Apart" LTD, Full-time

My main responsibilities included managing contracts with clients and suppliers, monitoring accounts receivable and accounts payable, and representing my company's interests at banks and regulatory authorities.

May 2013 - Jan 2017 St Petersburg, Russia Sales Manager, "Drive" LTD, Full-time

My responsibilities included processing orders from wholesale customers, monitoring the shipment of goods to customers, monitoring accounts receivable, expanding the supplier base, buying spare parts from partners, working with complaints, and resolving conflict situations with customers and suppliers.

Sep 2011 - May 2013

Travel Agent, "Marina Club" LTD

Magnitogorsk, Russia My main responsibilities were working with customer requests, selection and sale of tours and air tickets. During my work, I created and managed groups in social networks, created an extensive electronic database of hotels with detailed descriptions for the most popular tourist destinations.

Aug 2010 - Jan 2011 Magnitogorsk, Russia **Sales assistant, Mobile Phone Accessory Shop "Sotovik-M"**Selling mobile phones, SIM cards and accessories, fulfillment of sales plan.

#### **Education**

Sep 2006 – Jun 2012

Russian International Academy of Tourism Specialist, Organizational Management

# Licenses & certifications

Feb 2024	Python: Basics and application Credential: <a href="https://stepik.org/cert/2368892?lang=en">https://stepik.org/cert/2368892?lang=en</a>
Jun 2023	English GCSE - Grade 7
Jun 2020	Google IT Support Professional Certificate, Coursera Credential: <a href="https://coursera.org/share/123232d60839e1e4d4ed90bdbaf3e50a">https://coursera.org/share/123232d60839e1e4d4ed90bdbaf3e50a</a>
Oct 2019	Web development for beginners: HTML and CSS Credential: <a href="https://stepik.org/cert/231917?lang=en">https://stepik.org/cert/231917?lang=en</a>
Aug 2019	Python Programming Credential: <a href="https://stepik.org/cert/214012?lang=en">https://stepik.org/cert/214012?lang=en</a>
Feb 2019	Introduction to Linux Credential: <a href="https://stepik.org/cert/168792?lang=en">https://stepik.org/cert/168792?lang=en</a>
Key skills	
	<ul> <li>Adaptability</li> <li>Quick learner</li> <li>Dedication</li> <li>Attention to details</li> <li>Python</li> <li>Flask</li> <li>HTML/CSS (basic)</li> <li>MS Office</li> </ul>
Languages	

English, Russian, French